<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Science on </title>
    <link>http://paulsec.github.io/categories/data-science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Science on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 21:05:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://paulsec.github.io/categories/data-science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Incidents clustering using TF-IDF and KMeans</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/incidents_clustering_101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 21:05:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/incidents_clustering_101/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://paulsec.github.io/img/clusters.png&#34; alt=&#34;Incidents clustering&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Incident clustering, also known as event clustering or anomaly clustering, is a technique used in data analysis and machine learning to group similar incidents or events together based on their characteristics or patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In order to deep dive into this, we used &lt;code&gt;sklearn&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;matplotlib&lt;/code&gt; to both do machine learning and visualize results in an easy way.&#xA;In few words:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Scikit-learn is a powerful and popular open-source machine learning library in Python. It provides a wide range of tools for various machine learning tasks such as classification, regression, clustering, dimensionality reduction, and more. Scikit-learn is built on top of other Python libraries like NumPy, SciPy, and matplotlib and integrates well with the scientific Python ecosystem.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Matplotlib is a 2D plotting library in Python that allows you to create a wide variety of static, animated, and interactive visualizations. It is highly customizable and can be used to visualize data in the form of line plots, scatter plots, bar plots, histograms, and more.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The main idea is quite simple - clustering incidents and try to find &amp;ldquo;clusters&amp;rdquo; - aka ~incidents categories so that we group them and go from 900 dedicated incidents to 10 categories, easier when we want to tackle big subjects which will ease our work in the upcoming days.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
