<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 21:01:09 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://paulsec.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of side projects : Keep tinkering 🥷</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/the-benefits-of-a-side-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 21:01:09 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/the-benefits-of-a-side-project/</guid>
      <description>Since 2017, I have created and been maintaining cfptime.org, a community-driven project aimed at centralizing call-for-papers information for information security conferences.&#xA;Initially, my first goal was simple: we had an intern joining our team and who was about to work on Django Framework, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know it and I wanted to know the basics. Additionally, some other goals were simply to have fun, contribute something valuable to the community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making My Garage Door Smart (Meross MSG100 to TUBAUTO ProCom 7-3)</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/making-my-garage-door-smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 21:02:57 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/making-my-garage-door-smart/</guid>
      <description>Connecting Meross MSG100 to TUBAUTO ProCom 7-3 Garage Door: A Quick Guide&#xA;Modernizing your garage door to be smart-enabled can greatly enhance convenience and security. The Meross MSG100 Smart Wi-Fi Garage Door Opener offers an easy solution to connect your garage door to your home network, allowing you to control it remotely through the Meross application. If you have a TUBAUTO ProCom 7-3 garage door opener, integrating it with the Meross MSG100 is straightforward with the right guidance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitOps is the new black</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/gitops-the-new-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 20:24:13 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/gitops-the-new-black/</guid>
      <description>In the ever-evolving landscape of software development, GitOps has emerged as a powerful paradigm, initially associated with cloud-native applications. However, its significance personally extends beyond the realms of modern, containerized environments. GitOps has proven to be a valuable concept for legacy (or &amp;ldquo;more traditional&amp;rdquo;) applications too, providing a bridge that captures technical expertise and establishes deterministic operations resulting in a better quality of service.&#xA;The Essence of GitOps GitOps is fundamentally rooted in the principles of declarative infrastructure and version control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incidents clustering using TF-IDF and KMeans</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/incidents_clustering_101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 21:05:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/incidents_clustering_101/</guid>
      <description>Incident clustering, also known as event clustering or anomaly clustering, is a technique used in data analysis and machine learning to group similar incidents or events together based on their characteristics or patterns.&#xA;In order to deep dive into this, we used sklearn and matplotlib to both do machine learning and visualize results in an easy way. In few words:&#xA;Scikit-learn is a powerful and popular open-source machine learning library in Python.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I quitted Infosec and I couldn&#39;t be happier.</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/i-quitted-infosec/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 20:00:24 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/i-quitted-infosec/</guid>
      <description>This article aims at providing you some insights about the experience I had in the &amp;ldquo;infosec world&amp;rdquo; for the past few years. I had an amazing journey and grateful for everything that happened. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong with the title, even if the road was sometimes &amp;ldquo;bumpy&amp;rdquo; (aka &amp;lsquo;bad&amp;rsquo; experiences), I got some good lessons learnt through them and live by them. I am not trying to convince anyone with this article, except just do what&amp;rsquo;s good for you and preserve yourself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A quick primer on Frida and Android Instrumentation</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/frida-android-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 17:25:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/frida-android-primer/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone!&#xA;Here is a pretty quick blog post on some Frida/Objection things I&amp;rsquo;ve been tinkering with.&#xA;I had this Android application which had premium features and wanted to understand how that mechanism worked and if it was robust enough. Let&amp;rsquo;s see what was the journey on how I&amp;rsquo;ve bypassed it using Frida.&#xA;After disassembling the application with Jadx, I was able to perform a simple grep -r -i &#39;premium&#39; .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#34;DevOps&#34; ramblings and observations</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/devoops-ramblings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 14:40:19 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/devoops-ramblings/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;DevOps&amp;rdquo; movement started &amp;ldquo;publicly&amp;rdquo; (first time we heard this term) circa 2007. Based on that, we (you?) might think that in 2021 that thing is utterly oudated but I totally disagree and I thought I would share some thoughts about DevOps in 2021, and what it means in real life.&#xA;I am quite uncomfortable using the word &amp;ldquo;DevOps&amp;rdquo;. I&amp;rsquo;m serious. I guess it&amp;rsquo;s because we&amp;rsquo;re putting so many things behind it and I feel we might have lost track of the real sense behind that term - &amp;ldquo;DevOps&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Instrumentation with Smali: A survival guide</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/android-smali-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 15:29:02 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/android-smali-primer/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone!&#xA;This article aims at providing you survival steps while tinkering around with Smali &amp;amp; Android applications. The name of the original application I did my search on will remain secret but I created a dummy application doing the same so that you can do it on your own. The link of the MainActivity.java and MainActivity.smali is here&#xA;Create a dummy application with Android Studio and just import this. PLACEHOLDER_* strings will have to be replaced with proper ones if you want to try.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling &#39;Cleartext Not Permitted&#39; error in Ionic v5</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/ionic-cleartext-not-permitted/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 17:29:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/ionic-cleartext-not-permitted/</guid>
      <description>While developing/maintaining the WHID Mobile Injector app, it turns out that I received messages and issues on Github telling me that users were:&#xA;Able to access the ESPloit interface through the browser but not through the app and the toggle in the side-menu was staying RED (meaning it is unable to connect to the ESPloit interface). Weird.&#xA;After some investigations, I was able to reproduce the issue on some phones at home, and while looking at logcat, I saw some strange lines like this:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastAPI &#43; Zeit.co = 🚀</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/fastapi_plus_zeit_serverless_fu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 20:12:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/fastapi_plus_zeit_serverless_fu/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone,&#xA;I will talk about some experiments I did with FastAPI and deploying on Zeit.co.&#xA;Context: For one side-project, I needed a simple way to retrieve the information from a specific Android application (eg. io.shodan.app) on the Google Store and a download link from APKPure (if any).&#xA;I thought that this would have been a great playground to get my hands on FastAPI, a very promising framework that I never had time to play with.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working with Events on Ionic 5 </title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/ionic-5-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 16:52:42 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/ionic-5-events/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone,&#xA;Here is a small blog post where I needed to work on an Ionic v5 project where (Angular) events were/are not working anymore.&#xA;Context: Basically, I was working on the side-menu &amp;lsquo;starter&amp;rsquo; where I wanted the side-menu to automatically update with the user&amp;rsquo;s username after logging in.&#xA;Beforehand, in order to use the Events, it was as simple as:&#xA;import { Events } from &amp;#39;@ionic/angular&amp;#39;; And finally work on your logic, but this got removed in Ionic 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kafka Experiments</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/kafka-experiments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 21:22:27 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/kafka-experiments/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone,&#xA;Here is a small blog post regarding Kafka experiments and &amp;ldquo;foundations&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;ve started working on. I will also take the opportunity to thank Maxence S. (https://twitter.com/maxenceschmitt) for his precious help on this topic.&#xA;Instanciating the Jungle! ZooKeeper and Kafka First off, I instanciated a Kafka (and ZooKeeper) instance&#xA;version: &amp;#39;2&amp;#39; services: zookeeper: image: wurstmeister/zookeeper:3.4.6 expose: - &amp;#34;2181&amp;#34; kafka: image: wurstmeister/kafka:2.11-2.0.0 depends_on: - zookeeper ports: - &amp;#34;9092:9092&amp;#34; environment: KAFKA_ADVERTISED_LISTENERS: PLAINTEXT://localhost:9092 KAFKA_LISTENERS: PLAINTEXT://0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy a Django application through Github Actions</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/deploy-django-github-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 14:02:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/deploy-django-github-actions/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone,&#xA;Here is a small article on how I successfully deployed my Django application through Github actions. Basically, what I needed was pretty simple, as soon as I push a new commit (on master), I want to:&#xA;connect through SSH on my remote server restart my cfptime service (which will do all the magic) My cfptime.org project is something like ~3 years old and at the beginning, I was deploying by hand and I created a bash script in order to ease this part and this is what it looked like:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Throttling policies on specific Django Viewset</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/django-viewset-throttling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 21:14:36 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/django-viewset-throttling/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone!&#xA;Here is a small article on some experiments I came across with the development of the new cfptime.org version. Goal: I needed to limit (anonymous) visitors on specific API endpoints (especially when creating/posting new Call For Papers to avoid flooding).&#xA;It turns out someone had similar thoughts and his blog post was pretty interested and helped me a lot. You can find the blog post here: https://www.pedaldrivenprogramming.com/2017/05/throttling-django-rest-framwork-viewsets/.&#xA;As the author states:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angular 8 Deployment within Github Actions Pipeline</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/angular8-deployment-pipeline-github-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 22:09:28 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/angular8-deployment-pipeline-github-actions/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone,&#xA;Here is a small article in order to explain you how I&amp;rsquo;ve deployed my Angular front-end to a server with Github actions.&#xA;Context: You might know that I am the developer behind cfptime.org and I&amp;rsquo;ve had the chance during the holidays to start re-developing the front-end using Angular. If you want to check what it looks like: https://beta.cfptime.org.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve longer been a CircleCI user but it seems that the free plan is not enough in order to build my Angular project (and trust me, it&amp;rsquo;s nothing ground-breaking, just couple of API calls and that&amp;rsquo;s it).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corelan Bootcamp Review</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/corelan-bootcamp-review-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 15:58:01 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/corelan-bootcamp-review-2018/</guid>
      <description>Time to relieve this blog and I think that a review of the Corelan Bootcamp training is the perfect occasion! I had in mind to try the OSCE certification and I felt I needed to go beyond just basic buffer overflows that you might come by with OSCP for example.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve had the chance to attend this training at Hack in Paris in June 2018 and I will try to give as much insights as I can without telling too much (because of NDA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSidesCBR 2017 CTF Write-Up: Derpchat</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/bsidescbr-2017-ctf-write-up-derpchat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/bsidescbr-2017-ctf-write-up-derpchat/</guid>
      <description>Hey there,&#xA;Following my serie of write-ups for the BSidesCBR challs, I will discuss the DerpChat one.&#xA;The instructions for this challenge were:&#xA;This web-based challenge was worth 275 points. Run docker-compose up and then browse to https://web.shell.dance:4443/. After browsing to https://web.shell.dance:4443/, I arrived on a registration/login page. I registered the account test/test and I finally got a page with two inputs: – One too search some messages I suppose – And one in the middle of the page stating: “Hello, could you please send me the link I was after?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSidesCBR 2017 CTF Write-Up: Needleinahaystack</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/bsidescbr-2017-ctf-write-up-needleinahaystack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/bsidescbr-2017-ctf-write-up-needleinahaystack/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone!&#xA;Such a long time since I didn’t post any article. Here is a quick write-up for the BSidesCBR Cryto challenge for “needleinahaystack”.&#xA;Before diving in the challenge, huge props to all the organizers and OJ for making those challs available to everyone with Docker containers and stuff (more write-ups coming soon).&#xA;If you guys want to give it a shot, here you go, all challs are available here. The challenge we will discuss in this post (needleinahaystack) is located here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running SSLScan on 5k servers taken from Alexa&#39;s top 10k</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/running-sslscan-on-5k-servers-taken-from-alexas-top-10k/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/running-sslscan-on-5k-servers-taken-from-alexas-top-10k/</guid>
      <description>After analyzing the HTTP Security Headers from the top 10k Alexa websites, I decided looking at the SSL Ciphers used on those websites.&#xA;These results are coming from a scan on port 443 for all those domains. Only 4715 servers replied.&#xA;The OpenSSL version installed on my server did not support SSLv2 so SSLv2 ciphers have not been detected.&#xA;Here are the results:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experiments with UPnP</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/experiments-with-upnp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/experiments-with-upnp/</guid>
      <description>This post deals with recent observations regarding UPnP (Universal Plug and Play) protocol &amp;amp; Routers. In few words, thanks to this protocol, devices (such as file sharing services, games, ..) can be easily connected/deployed.&#xA;First, I started to do research on my box to find relevant UPnP functionalities by hand, found some but I had trouble to exploit them. Few days ago, David Middlehurst released a tool called &amp;ldquo;UPnP Pentest Toolkit&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kioptrix 3 Write-up</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/kioptrix-3-write-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/kioptrix-3-write-up/</guid>
      <description>This has been some long time I haven&amp;rsquo;t written another write-up. This one&amp;rsquo;s for Kioptrix 3 that you can find here.&#xA;Host Discovery $ nmap -sP 192.168.56.1/24 and we got the IP address : 192.168.56.101.&#xA;As it was explained, you need to add 192.168.56.101 kioptrix3.com in your /etc/hosts.&#xA;Fingerprinting Then, let&amp;rsquo;s find what kind of services are running on the host machine.&#xA;$ nmap 192.168.56.101 -sV -A Starting Nmap 6.46 ( http://nmap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diving into XSS googles game</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/diving-into-xss-googles-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/diving-into-xss-googles-game/</guid>
      <description>Hi there, this post deals with the game released by Google few days ago about XSS vulnerabilities that you can find here.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ll enumerate some of the solution I found on the Internet which were (in my opnion) interesting/fun. This post contains the solutions for all levels. Big spoil.&#xA;Level 1: Hello, world of XSS Well, this one was obvious:&#xA;&amp;lt;script&amp;gt;alert(1);&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; Level 2: Persistence is key For this one, you had different options:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bobby Write-up</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/bobby-write-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/bobby-write-up/</guid>
      <description>Hi there,&#xA;Quick blog post on the VM &amp;ldquo;Bobby&amp;rdquo; which is once of the nicest VM I did so far.&#xA;Discovery The first step is always the same: discovering the machine on the network. To do so:&#xA;$ nmap -sV 192.168.1.1/24 I managed to retrieve the IP address: 192.168.1.11.&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s start to fingerprint the different services to exploit it.&#xA;Fingerprinting Then, I used Nmap to retrieve the services running:&#xA;$ nmap -sV 192.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTTP Security Headers on top 10k Alexa websites</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/http-security-headers-on-top-10k-alexa-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/http-security-headers-on-top-10k-alexa-websites/</guid>
      <description>EDIT: Added statistics of max-age option.&#xA;Hi there,&#xA;This blog post deals with HTTP Security Headers on top 10k Alexa websites. Based on this discussion on netsec, I decided to do some statistics on Alexa ranking.&#xA;To do this study, I did a GET HTTP Request and saved the headers in the HTTP response. This has been done using Python.&#xA;First of all, I scanned 10000 hosts. 555 hosts didn&amp;rsquo;t respond so those statistics are based on 9445 hosts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind HQL Injection in REST API using H2 DMBS</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/blind-hql-injection-in-rest-api-using-h2-dbms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/blind-hql-injection-in-rest-api-using-h2-dbms/</guid>
      <description>This post deals with some research I just did regarding (Blind) HQL injections with H2 as the DataBase Management System.&#xA;First, you should read this post which gives some really useful information regarding HQL injections in general: HQL for pentesters.&#xA;During the assessment, I checked the API calls by using Burp as a proxy and one call was:&#xA;http://application/API/Users/?req=id=1 The output was a JSON response, such as:&#xA;[{user: &amp;#34;admin&amp;#34;, id: &amp;#34;1&amp;#34;, firstName:&amp;#34;Admin&amp;#34;}] If you changed the id with the numeric value 2, and so on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSides Slides - CSRFT</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/bsides-slides-csrft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/bsides-slides-csrft/</guid>
      <description>Hey,&#xA;Just a quick post to give you the link to my slides for BSides London today: Here Don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate if you have any feedback, or any good feature.&#xA;You can reach me either on Github and Twitter&#xA;Just few words about the conference which was absolutely amazing. Some really great people were here, good atmosphere and people were really helpful.&#xA;For sure, I&amp;rsquo;ll attend it next year.&#xA;Cheers,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BWApp Write-Up</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/bwapp-write-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/bwapp-write-up/</guid>
      <description>This post contains the steps to get a root shell with bWapp VM&#xA;Host discovery As always, we need to discover where the machine is on our network. To do so, let&amp;rsquo;s use Nmap:&#xA;nmap -sP 192.168.1.1/24 Fingerprinting After getting the IP address (192.168.1.10), we need to do some fingerprinting.&#xA;nmap -sV 192.168.1.10 Fig. Nmap scan result&#xA;A lot of services were open, such as: VNC, FTP, etc.&#xA;As I saw it in the scan report, I decided to scan the port 80 with Nikto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scream Write-up</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/scream-write-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/scream-write-up/</guid>
      <description>This post contains the steps to get a root shell with Scream VM&#xA;This VM can he found here. Have a look to find even more VMs. But before starting the report, I&amp;rsquo;d like to congratulate g0tmi1k for his awesome tool : VulnInjector.&#xA;Ok, let&amp;rsquo;s do this write-up !&#xA;Host discovery As always, we need to discover where the machine is on our network. To do so, let&amp;rsquo;s use Nmap:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting KB Vulnerable Web App 1 Write-Up</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/exploit-kb-vulnerable-web-app-1-write-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/exploit-kb-vulnerable-web-app-1-write-up/</guid>
      <description>This post contains the steps to get a root shell with Exploit KB Vulnerable Web App 1 VM&#xA;This VM can he found here. Have a look to find even more VMs&#xA;Host discovery First, we need to discover where the machine is on our network. To do so, let&amp;rsquo;s use Nmap:&#xA;nmap -sP 192.168.1.1/24 Fingerprinting After getting the IP address, we need to do some fingerprinting.&#xA;nmap -sV 192.168.1.23 Fig.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kioptrix 2 Write-up</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/kioptrix-2-write-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/kioptrix-2-write-up/</guid>
      <description>This post contains the steps to get a root shell with Kioptrix level 2 VM&#xA;This VM can he found here. Have a look to find even more VMs&#xA;Host discovery First, we need to discover where the machine is on our network. To do so, let&amp;rsquo;s use Nmap:&#xA;nmap -sP 192.168.1.1/24 Fingerprinting After getting the IP address, we need to do some fingerprinting.&#xA;nmap -sV 192.168.1.42 Fig. Nmap scan result</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kioptrix 1 Write-up</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/kioptrix-1-write-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/kioptrix-1-write-up/</guid>
      <description>This post contains the steps to get a root shell with Kioptrix level 1 VM&#xA;This VM can he found here. Have a look to find even more VMs&#xA;Host discovery First, we need to discover where the machine is on our network. To do so, let&amp;rsquo;s use Nmap:&#xA;nmap -sP 192.168.1.1/24 Fingerprinting After getting the IP address, we need to do some fingerprinting.&#xA;nmap -sV 192.168.1.2 Fig. Nmap scan result</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SecOS-1 First VM Out</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/secos-1-first-vm-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/secos-1-first-vm-out/</guid>
      <description>Hey there,&#xA;Quick blog post for the first VM I created to experiment some of your pentesting skills.&#xA;The idea grew up when I developed some security tools (especially the one (CSRFT) I presented at BSides London few weeks ago) to create a legal environment where you could try it out.&#xA;I really liked creating this Boot2root VM. So, I&amp;rsquo;ll create few more that will rely on each other so keep the flags because you&amp;rsquo;ll need it for the next ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updating OpenFuck Exploit</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/updating-openfuck-exploit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/updating-openfuck-exploit/</guid>
      <description>This blog post will be quite fast and will provide you the steps to update the OpenFuck exploit.&#xA;This exploit is pretty old but you might need it if you have fun with some vulnerable VMs. Not giving any hint. :-)&#xA;Thanks to this blog, I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to update the exploit.&#xA;Here are the steps to make this work :&#xA;1) Add those headers : #include &amp;lt;openssl/rc4.h&amp;gt; #include &amp;lt;openssl/md5.h&amp;gt; 2) Update the URL of the C file.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VulnOS Write-up</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/vulnos-write-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/vulnos-write-up/</guid>
      <description>This contains the solution of the VM: VulnOS.&#xA;This is my first write-up for a VM and I&amp;rsquo;m doing it for VulnOS which is hosted on VulnHub (Great resource if you want to improve your pentesting skills).&#xA;In this &amp;rsquo;tutorial&amp;rsquo;, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna give you the steps I reproduced to get a shell on the machine.&#xA;Discovery First, start by scanning the network to discover where&amp;rsquo;s the host.&#xA;nmap -sV 192.168.56.1/24 Starting Nmap 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python &#43; Transmission daemon = Download easily your favorite TV Show</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/python-plus-transmission-daemon-equals-download-easily-your-favorite-tv-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/python-plus-transmission-daemon-equals-download-easily-your-favorite-tv-show/</guid>
      <description>This post is about my last project : my TV Show Manager.&#xA;I decided to start it because I wanted something really simple to download my favorite TV Shows. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll explain step by step how to reproduce it at home.&#xA;Basically, with this tutorial you&amp;rsquo;ll set up your Raspberry box by :&#xA;Installing / set-uping transmission-daemon Getting one of my latest project TVShowManager that uses my EZTV Python API.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XSS Callback</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/xss-callback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/xss-callback/</guid>
      <description>This post deals with a project I developed : XSS Callback.&#xA;This is not going to be (at least, I hope) a boring post about XSS exploitation. No.&#xA;Well, one scenario of using XSS would be to steal victim&amp;rsquo;s cookie and access the page through his session. This technique is called Session Hijacking. Ok fair enough.&#xA;However, some issues are present using this technique, let&amp;rsquo;s take an example :&#xA;You target a website Unfortunately, it&amp;rsquo;s too late (or too early depending on your situation) and you go to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dealing with HTML submits conflicts</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/dealing-with-html-submits-conflict/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/dealing-with-html-submits-conflict/</guid>
      <description>This first post is related with one of my project : CSRFT. CSRFT is a Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerabilities Toolkit.&#xA;My toolkit allows you to exploit either GET and POST HTTP Requests. During some testings, I had issues with some specific forms.&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s take an example of such form :&#xA;&amp;lt;form action=&amp;#34;http://website.com/blog/&amp;#34; id=&amp;#34;form&amp;#34; method=&amp;#34;get&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;label class=&amp;#34;assistive-text&amp;#34; for=&amp;#34;s&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Search&amp;lt;/label&amp;gt; &amp;lt;input class=&amp;#34;field&amp;#34; id=&amp;#34;s&amp;#34; name=&amp;#34;s&amp;#34; placeholder=&amp;#34;Search&amp;#34; type=&amp;#34;text&amp;#34; value=&amp;#34;Search Value&amp;#34;/&amp;gt; &amp;lt;input class=&amp;#34;submit&amp;#34; id=&amp;#34;searchsubmit&amp;#34; name=&amp;#34;submit&amp;#34; type=&amp;#34;submit&amp;#34; value=&amp;#34;Search&amp;#34;/&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/form&amp;gt; The code injected on the page to submit the form was like that :</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starting my own blog</title>
      <link>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/starting-my-own-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://paulsec.github.io/posts/starting-my-own-blog/</guid>
      <description>Starting my own blog has been something I really wanted to do. I&amp;rsquo;ll add post related to my different projects but also on Web security.&#xA;Here are my different motivations :&#xA;1. Provide a portfolio of my different projects. 2. Explain some problems I had and provide the solution 3. Talk about some geek stuffs. Let&amp;rsquo;s see :) Hope you&amp;rsquo;ll have fun to read me. Cheers and see you soon.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
